There have been all sorts of ideas and schemes cooked up to try and clean up that oil spill.
We found one that has nothing to do with giant sponges or even human hair.
It's an engine.
And as our business and tech reporter Scott Budman shows us, it runs on what's in the
Gulf right now.
With as much as 800,000 gallons of crude oil a day spilling into the Gulf, the situation
is desperate.
How do we get rid of all this oil?
Here we go.
Here's one idea, an engine that runs on a mix of 80% seawater and 20% oil, like what
you see in the Gulf.
This would be the right time to put this forward.
Charles Ostman is a physicist helping to test the engine.
He says it's not that complicated and that it could work.
In my vision, I would see an array of these things on board, just feed the materials through
there and keep pulling out useful materials.
exactly what I'd be doing. The mix of oil and water burns cleaner than what's in our cars or
lawnmowers. And it did burn clean for us up to a point. But maybe all of this will lead to more
ideas like this. Maybe the bright side of this is that now finally people that would have never
looked at this before saying wait a minute maybe there are those solutions let's give it a second
try. So in my mind that's the positive side of this otherwise very dark circumstance. Bad news
leading to inventors firing up new solutions in santa clara scott budman nbc bay area news
the group that invented the oil and water engine contacted british petroleum
VP wrote back saying, no thanks.