This is Talk for Food.
Your portal into quantum possibility.
I'm Adam Abraham.
Each week I'll be your guide on this expedition
where we'll explore the near and far reaches
of this thing called life on Earth and beyond.
talk for food is brought to you by philo's books publishers of i am my body not a freed man an
emancipation proclamation and producers of understanding mms conversations with jim
the only feature-length documentary on the subject of the miracle mineral supplement
on Earth.
We don't get any liquid fuel to our engines or furnaces.
All it is is a vapor.
By pulling a vacuum, which has been removed from most books,
from 1955 on, all vacuum technology that would help mankind was removed.
Actually, this is not a plastic bottle.
it is combination of gas diesel and kerosene and if you put this in an
electric element underneath it and let it melt the vapors are going to get off
it or the vapors for gas diesel kerosene so if you redistill this back into fuel
you have the fuel to run engines power plants whatever you want with no
pollution if you're using a geek so why are we burying all the plastic and
garbage bits government doesn't want to see this technology is that it replaced they're pumping
more oil out they're buying more oil and they're trucking it and flipping it around
how about that of a teaser to introduce our guest for today's show those are the words and thoughts
of one paul pantone he was our guest on the show oh and before we get there hello again everyone
Thank you for joining us again for this week's edition of Talk for Food here on WebTalkRadio.net and iTunes and on video, wherever you are seeing it on video.
I'm Adam Abraham, and this is our time for journeying into realms of quantum possibility.
This is where we go inside. We go into the deepness of inner space to realize, find, connect with, and express the power that is within us to make the major and the all-important differences in what we see outside.
I have become, I am part of, I guess you say, a wave of people who are starting to see how to make change.
I've explored it for a while. I will continue to.
My life is literally going to be about change. It's been about it.
And not simply anarchist change, not simply destroying.
It's basically how do you recreate what you want in life?
Not something that takes away from others, not something that is meting out some vengeance for some perceived insults, not in anger, but simply creating for the joy of it, creating a life, creating an experience, creating adventure for the simple fact that you can.
Having experiences that are meaningful to you.
Maybe there is a vision.
We are creative beings.
We're creative people.
We create by, one, the desire to do so.
Secondly, by the intention to do so.
And thirdly, you might say by the will.
And this is not something we tend to teach.
It certainly has taken me a while to kind of get to be really clear
that that's how we do it because the imagination we use our imaginations to create our reality to
create our world and our imagination has no judgment as to the rightness the wrongness
the goodness or the bad of it it is simply what it is because it is all simply information
nothing better nothing worse it all needs to be in order for any of it to be so within that
milieu how often do you get to someone using the word milieu in a sentence uh-huh uh in that milieu
we have full spectrum full potential full scope full list of options of what we can do in terms
possibilities. And all of them exist when we exist. So, if you're out there in pain right now
and you're in disease of some type, there is a part of you that is not. All right? If you are
right now scuffling to make ends meet, there is a part of you that's doing just fine.
Now, how do you get to that part?
Well, the first part is that if you think that what you're doing right now is all there is,
you're stuck there, okay?
But you're stuck by your own sticking.
You're stuck by your own thinking and your own believing.
You can change your beliefs.
You can change how you think.
You can change your energy.
And just, I won't say it's as simply as changing channels as you would on a dial of a radio or a TV, but the principles are the same.
All of those other realities, all those other options exist the moment that you exist.
And so if you at least become aware, if sometimes, you know, say you stumbled across, stumbled upon this conversation and you hear this guy talking about, gee, there's a part of you that actually is not dealing with this problem that you're so stuck in right now.
Well, it's you too.
Not you too, but it's you too.
And if you want to be expressing that portion of you in the moment, here and now, you've got to resonate with the thinking and with the vision and with the scope of possibilities and potentials that that part of you feels is okay.
because a part of you that you're expressing right now
apparently don't think it's possible or it's okay.
It's all possible.
It's all okay.
And your imagination has no judgment whatsoever.
And it will create for you what you create,
what you imagine, what you sense is possible for you.
and so when you change what you sense is possible for you you will then change your experience of
what happens of what you what comes to you what moments become yours in space and time
so that's a little piece that's that's part of the scenario and i don't know gee i got into that but
i started off with a clip from paul pantone and paul i met at the extraordinary technology
conference, and we interviewed him. I interviewed him. I met him. We had a great time. I want to
tell you right now, he wasn't all that happy with how I did my interview, how I showed it,
how I presented it, because I talk too much, all right? Well, it's my show, all right? I make no
apologies for doing that. If I got something to say, I got something to say, and I do it.
but he did like it well enough
or he saw the potential of me well enough
to invite me to come and spend more time with him
and oh did I jump at that
Paul is an amazing man
he has done some amazing things
and he has seen some amazing things
that are possible
and he's doing what he can
as we are all doing what we can
to make changes occur
and what not just again destroying change i guess that's how i got in that tangent in the first
place basically changes that are beneficial changes that will actually um resolve many of
the concerns that we have environmentally energy wise he has come he has answers and yet his light
if you will, has in a lot of respects been shunned. He developed something he calls GEET,
G-E-E-T, Global Environmental Energy Technology. And I acknowledge, I said before, I didn't know
what it was then. I have a much better feeling for it now after having spent some time with him.
And so what we're going to do on this show is a couple of things.
You, as listeners and viewers of Talk for Food, you're getting a preview because now you're going to hear my conversation with him and our dialogue.
Because this show is going to be my conversation with Paul Pantone on his ground in Oklahoma.
I went and spent several days with him and I spent two days shooting.
I got about four hours of footage.
Now, here's my plan, and I'm telling you this now.
You can think about it right now.
You can plan on it now.
You're getting my dialogue here, and you hear the commercials and everything else
because this is my radio show, all right?
But what you are hearing and or seeing, this is all done on camera,
is going to be part of a video, a four DVD video to be called Indelible Promise.
And I'll talk about why I came up with that name because there is something very much indelible
about what Paul has to say. And it is written on our souls. As far as I'm concerned, it cannot be
erased. It cannot be smudged off. It can't be ignored or pushed under a carpet. There are some
things about life that Paul Pantone knows and that he sat down with me to share. We sat next
to a window in front of a refrigerator and that's what you're going to see. The light from the window
next to him and the refrigerator behind him. But listen to what the man has to say. So we're going
take a break. I'm going to give you a couple additional beginnings here and there. But when
we come back on the other side, we're going to hear and visit with Paul Pantone down in the
heartland when Talk for Food returns on web at talkradio.net. American adventurer Jim Humble
discovered how a simple chemical compound and powerful oxidizer, chlorine dioxide, could be
effectively used to reduce toxicity within the human body the buzz on jim's discovery mms miracle
mineral supplement is spreading but not the understanding until now understanding mms
conversations with jim humble is a new dvd available only at understanding-mms.com
the understanding mms dvd will show how you can be part of your own solution to toxicity
Here's the documentary producer.
This is Adam Abraham inviting you to get informed and help others to be informed of this amazing way to reduce the body's load of toxins, harmful microorganisms and pathogens from the waters inside our body.
Get your understanding today for only $29.95 at understanding-mms.com.
That's understanding-mms.com.
Use passcode RBN to receive 10% off.
Our health really depends on it.
all right this edition of this segment of talk for food get started on web talk radio dot net
with adam abraham and okay i've given you the intro to paul pantone developer of geet
And I'll tell you, his website is geetinternational.com, G-E-E-T.
I spent several days with him.
And the first part of our conversation, oh, I'll tell you this.
The first day, I spent three days down there.
The first day, we just talked and talked and talked and talked.
And I frankly wish I had that on camera.
He told me just about some amazing things.
But, okay, that's just going to have to be some other time and another visit.
But what is to follow will be part of a four DVD video to be called Indelible Promise.
And we've already set up a website called IndeliblePromise.com.
And you can see the information there and what we've got right there.
But the video will be edited.
So a lot of what you're going to hear now will not be in there.
You're going to be getting Paul.
You will be getting less of me in the video, but this is still my show, so you're getting me on it.
Let's start it. We began by talking about inventor's syndrome.
He had talked about it the day before, and given the fact that Paul is a master inventor, he's a visionary,
and given how much invention has changed our world
and at the same time how the obstruction of invention
is blocking the further changing in a beneficial way of our world,
it's really important, I feel, to start by talking about inventor syndrome
and really appreciating what inventors do in their mind.
So this is where we start and the rest speaks for itself.
inventor syndrome is something I came up with years ago and it would make it
really good book or movie because every inventor I met seemed to have a
personality disorder and when I stood back and observed it it was much like an
artist so I wanted to see how far I could challenge this so what I did is I
hired an artist to come to my home and I said I want to pay you by the hour to
paint a picture for me okay and she said well okay no one's ever done that I said well I want
you to take and I went over to the wall and I drew a one foot by foot and a half area I said
I want you to paint me a forest right here well it was where I could sit from my desk and see it
and she went over there and started painting the forest and after she got it almost done
I could see she was giving it the last minute detailed look I walked over and I said you know
want i know you spent two days doing this but i really want it bigger can you make it two feet
by three feet okay well no it's the same thing if you go to an inventor and say well i see what
you built but i want it this way it's upsetting to the inventor accept what he has built and
complete your deal on that because for an artist that picture usually is removable it's not painted
onto a solid object right it's not yours when they're done with it it's theirs until you buy
it well i paid her by the hour i put a twist to it so as she walked out at the end of the day it
was my picture now after i got her to paint it a little bigger i said no that's still not big
enough can we go six feet and then i came in a few days later let's make it the whole wall
floor to ceiling right well i kept her there for a month no matter what she did i said oh you know
what let's move that pine tree over six inches she'd have to paint the sky back in everything
all back in and move the she kept doing it over and over until i finally got her to the point of
snapping and when i saw the tears i said okay this was just a test i wanted to see emotionally
as an artist because i'm an inventor and i like to look at myself as an artist with what i'm doing
right but i saw the same problem with myself that i do with other inventors that you build something
and no matter how pretty that something looks well it should have been this way i should have added
this here there should have been a valve here this should have been rounded edges no matter
what it is there's always a way to improve upon it so you'll never get a finished product from
the inventor the canvas is still fluid huh still works doesn't have to do but they're never complete
they're never happy with their final product but the problem is if you're an investor or someone
who wants to market that technology you go to that inventor and say well yeah that's all right
but it needs to be cleaned up it needs this it needs this he's holding that because that's his
baby you're not happy with his baby he doesn't want to give you his baby so all of a sudden that
price tag of common sense goes out the window and it's i want a zillion dollars for it right right
well it's not worth that it's not ready to market yet it needs work well i don't want to work with
you. I'm sorry. But an inventor, when he's told it's not good enough, all of a sudden
his ego is crushed. He feels like an artist. That's not what I want. I want something different.
Well, this is what I have. Leave. And it's that attitude. A lot of the investors that
come in want to dress up and impress the inventor, which is the dumbest thing in the world you
can do showing up in a nice car flashy clothes when the guy is starving to death every penny
he makes is going into an invention his baby and if he sees you're all that successful and you're
not coming in to offer him something up front it hurts him you've already got it all you're trying
to take what i have so you have more no look at it from his perspective he'd be a lot happier if
If you pulled up in an older car, an older truck,
cut out in casual clothes,
they can still be nice new clothes,
but something a lot more casual,
and be on his level.
Let him tell you what he's invented and how it works.
You may see a million other applications for it,
but if he can't, don't confuse him.
Give him praise for what he's done,
and then the very next thing you want to do
before you start talking about money
and how much you can raise,
sit down with the man and say joe what is it going to take for you to feed your family and you know
keep the power on and everything else you need what are your basic needs here and when he comes
up with well i need 200 for this and 300 for that they always underestimate inventors are just that
nature they're inclined to look at what their specific needs are of the moment without without
really foresight you got it so they're going to sit there well i need 800 a month well chances
are they need 1600 a month so if you offer them saying you know what i'd like to help you out and
work with you but let's not worry about new and improved or making it better why don't i go ahead
and we'll start marketing this model give me four months or six months to get everything set up but
in the meantime let's take care of your needs you just want a friend because nobody else wants to
take care of his knees they want to take the product and they want him to make it better
don't worry about making it better you can hire an engineer to modify it by the hour whatever it
takes to put a pretty cover on it right don't worry about letting the inventor do it unless
you never want to go to market inventors don't really care about the market although they say
they do they say they want to get the product out there they're more interested in making it perfect
They want their baby to be perfect.
Wow, which means it can be a perpetual process.
I've seen inventors that have sent their whole life on one or two products, never got them to the marketplace.
And here they are in their 70s and 80s, and they're still playing with it like they were 45 years ago.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Men, and many men, I'd say inventors, or mostly men, I'd have to say, in history.
I could be wrong.
I could be sexist with that, okay.
So men can be the, or typically are the inventor types, but that is a men's equivalent to giving birth as well, you know.
Yes.
They're like their mothers, you know, to this child.
It's their baby.
Right.
And I don't mean to correct you on this, because it's a funny thing you say that.
During the George Norris show, I had made the comment that I believe there are more women inventors out there than there are men.
Because normally the women I meet are much more creative.
and when they want something built for the kitchen they don't ask the husband to do it
they go start cutting stuff up taping it together gluing it together and they make it when the kids
toys break they fix it while daddy's at work daddy doesn't look at all the things mommy does
right right so women are much more creative when i was building houses in california i had we went
through 178 houses in seven years buying and selling i didn't design i would ask my wife
and my son hey what do you think about this place well you know dad it'd look really neat if you did
this my wife said well it'd really look pretty if you put this here and this here and i'd be
sitting over there thinking i didn't say that okay if you think it'd look pretty we'll give it a shot
you decorate i'll just build well i'd go supervise the crew would get the rough end done she'd come
in there and decorate it out every place she'd done everybody loved her work but all the additions
that my son said let's add a porch here let's do this here we chose his path on many of the physical
things because a six-year-old has a very open mind and everybody who saw the finished product
loved those grand entryways and and the holes cut through the ceiling indirect lighting everything
he had suggested was great helped sell houses so i listened to the women and children now i found
that little children especially are the best inventors there are if we just allow them the
right to open their mouth and communicate with us the problem is from the time they're born we tell
them come on say daddy say mommy come on talk and the minute they start talking it's not now i'm
busy or shut up i've got things to do go play and then when they come up with a story and say hey
you know there's just a gnome out in the garden he's i don't have time for stuff like that don't
Don't make up stuff.
Wait a minute.
You're imaginary friends.
Yeah.
What do you mean I can't have an imaginary friend?
You're the one telling me from the time I was born about Jack and the Beanstalk and
Fairy Godmothers and all these things and the witches.
You can make up stuff?
And I hear you and mom talking about how you lie to IRS and you're going to lie to that
cop, you're going to lie to these people, yet you tell me not to make up stories?
Boy, I am confused.
And when I talk, you tell me to shut up.
Well, sure.
course our leaders get on in front of national tv and start telling the stories too so what do you
go do with that yeah so yeah you got it yeah what state of confusion are they in massive
do they want to share when they have an idea no how many of us have gone through life walked
into a store and said oh geez i thought of that 20 years ago i built one of those 15 years ago but
But did you ever go anywhere with it?
No.
Thought is in the universe.
And when a new thought for a new thing comes out, by whatever means,
it is out there for anyone who picks up on that thought.
But if I'm the only person who picked up on gait, yet the knowledge was out there,
I just had to put the pieces together.
Well, you're right.
And we are in this cultural thinking that advances to our society are going to come from a quote-unquote laboratory
or from someone who has some initials in front of or behind their names or some prestigious university.
And if we haven't had an improvement, then those folks haven't come up with it yet.
Right.
But that is not the history of our country, and that's not the reality.
But it's the programming we've had in this country since the 50s.
So many people, when I first told them, I can give you a 30% to 50% improvement with a snap, I'm just a piece of cake.
He is talking about gas mileage.
Getting double and triple, well, yeah, we can do it, but it's against the law.
Now, the government doesn't want that out there.
Can we teach it? Yeah, I can teach people.
But can I put it on your car? No.
That is also, I would imagine, a shock to most people when they hear this because we know everything you're hearing in the press and the media is about we have to reduce our dependence on fossil fuels.
The manufacturers are now just telling, oh, we're getting 40 miles per gallon with these little cracker box cars and stuff like that.
And we are believing that this is the cutting edge and the best we can do.
But you're saying something that there's actually a desire or a mandate against doing better than that,
even though there are mandates to do better.
Right.
We're not somehow.
In 1951, the Inventor Secrecy Act was published.
They control all the patents that go into the patent office.
If anything is above a certain percentage better than what is currently allowed,
it is automatically seized for military application first.
The inventor doesn't need to get compensated a penny.
Now, if the inventor puts up too much resistance, like we've seen,
some of those inventors are either put in nut houses or dead.
Yes.
And we've seen examples of both of those.
I've seen too many of my friends now that are dead.
Wow.
And personally, after three and a half years of maximum security detention,
without doing a crime, I'm sorry, I thought we lived in America.
Well, it's corporate America.
So what, maybe you've answered the question before I could get it out.
What is the, what's the thinking behind that?
What's, why is that happening when we are clearly,
where gasoline is now at this moment in the $3 to $4 per gallon range.
We've got emissions laws, you know, we've got mileage laws or guidelines.
But all of those can be exceeded by leaps and bounds in actuality.
Well, I think it goes back to a quote I heard from Jesse Ventura, I don't know if it's his quote or not, where he said, follow the money.
Well, you're going to find behind all of those money trails, all these inventions, like smog pumps, oh, you put this pump in and it reduces the emissions by 50%.
Well, if you have an emission stream pumping out 200 parts per million out the exhaust pipe and you pump in 50% more fresh air, which is coming from energy from the engine, so now you're reducing the engine by 3%, but you're putting 50% more fresh air in the exhaust pipe, yeah, you're only going to read 100 parts per million.
It's going to appear to the average idiot that, oh, we reduced emissions.
No, you didn't. You actually increased them.
Because, yeah, it's 50% less coming out, but you've got all this air coming out,
which is taking 3% of the energy from the engine to produce the airflow to the exhaust pipe.
So if we keep lying to the public about we're doing something when we aren't,
then you're never going to get ahead.
When they have technology, such as mine and many other inventors,
the government has stopped them from going forward because as long as they can control
the cash from oil we have a lot of rich politicians you don't want to take that
money away from congressmen senators and other people that's their livelihood i mean they can't
get by on their 200 to 400 000 a year i mean they need a little bit more money and as long as you
got a credit card in your wallet they want to charge it up on your credit cards boy we're just
getting started but we gotta stop for a break as this conversation with paul pantone and
basically a preview to indelible promise uh continues when we come back we'll get more into
what geet is as well as some of the implications of it that is what's so important about all this
but we'll be right back this is adam abraham with talk for food on web talk radio.net
Stay with us.
Jim Harshman is made to change from water treatment to water transformation technology,
having installed a unit from Photonic Water Systems for almost two years now.
He tells you in his own words what has changed.
Well, here's the problem we had when we built this house in 2005 or 2006.
we got it done and found out the water was extremely hard.
There was a lot of calcium buildup on the outside of the pool
and also into the misters inside the courtyard.
And so we know we had an issue with the water right off the bat.
So in trying to solve that, this is where we started to play around
with the different options that were in the market.
It kind of explored what was on the home shows at the different green shows
and also home shows that the Phoenix area was having.
And, you know, it was just a major problem, so we had to get it solved.
And we ran into the product, and I guess we can't say enough about it.
I mean, it took an intolerable scum problem, a white hard water problem,
and just neutralized it to where we don't have the buildup anymore.
We don't have the buildup on the pool, the courtyard, fountain,
or into the various systems that we have, such as your misters and your shower heads.
So it's 100% work.
Now, how it works, I have no idea, but it's not how it works that I'm worried about.
Available at photonicwater.com.
We come in all shapes and sizes, but for all our apparent differences, we share an important oneness.
I am my body.
Not.
Now your child can discover the oneness behind human diversity with I am my body.
From Phylos Books.
This progressive book written by Adam Abraham helps parents and teachers introduce some of the most basic human concepts and questions.
Celebrate the body and the spirit with I am my body.
Not.
Order now, just $19.95 plus shipping and handling.
I Am My Body, Knot, is available at phylos.com.
That's P-H-A-E-L-O-S dot com.
Order yours today.
Hi, this is Mary Meadows, and you're listening to Talk for Food on webtalkradio.net.
The second half of Talk for Food gets started right here and now on webtalkradio.net with Adam Abraham.
And we are talking with Paul Pantone, developer of GEET Global Environmental Energy Technology.
And it is a wide range of devices, but many of which are based around what's called plasma.
And we'll get into that.
It's called the fourth state of matter, and it has some amazing properties that is a part of you and I today, has always been, and yet you never hear about it.
Very, very interesting.
So we're going to talk more about that.
At any rate, let's get started.
We are talking about politicians and things like that.
This is from his actual experience.
I mean, he's not, this isn't sour grapes, this is simply what has been and oftentimes still what is, but also what needs to change.
Here he is.
See, for me, that's not good enough reason to not do the best, so to speak.
It might mean changing how they collect or something like that, but not simply just restrict this money.
We have been programmed, as a matter of fact, it was about six months ago, in the mail from the U.S. Post Office, which is a private corporation, it's not part of the U.S. government anymore, it said, if you receive any information by mail or communication that a device is really better than is believable, please report it to us so we can go seize the company, close it down.
There are a lot of scams out there, and anything that's better than what we tell you has to be a scam.
This is no exaggeration.
Anyone who's familiar with MMS, the Miracle Mineral Supplement, Master of Miracle Supplement of Jim Humbles,
the FDA has come down on it, and now working with the U.S. Postal Service,
they are attempting to build a case that some form of fraud or deception or scam has been perpetrated.
or that this particular product has been available or as some type of unapproved drug.
Bottom line is that their position is specious and their claims are false.
But the method is very consistent with exactly what he's just said.
We are programmed to believe that nothing can be better than what the government offers or approves.
There is no such thing as EPA approval.
I gave you a letter yesterday, and it clearly says it's a voluntary organization.
They don't have the right to approve, endorse, or certify any aftermarket product.
So where do they come up with, does it have EPA approval?
There is no such thing.
EPA is a glorified reporting agency, and it was put in for good reason, mind you,
that the Congress was tired of all these crazy inventors.
And there are a lot of them out there that are out there.
When they come up in front of Congress and say, I invented a perpetual motion machine.
You put five pounds in here, and as it turns, you add another five pounds,
and it just keeps spinning forever and ever and ever.
Well, they forgot gravity, friction, and a few other things.
But Congress got tired of hearing all these scatterbrained ideas and said,
we need a department to screen inventors and to make sure what they're putting on the cars is safe
and isn't going to kill somebody.
so go out and evaluate the best you can come up with your own standards now if
you shut that division down how many hundreds of thousands of people are
going to be unemployed well are they really employed now yeah right if
they're abusing their power and there's too many agencies out there that really
do not know if they're supposed to like the agency that was set up so that we
can make sure we're not importing oil it has grown what 500% per year for how
many years oh well sure and we're using more oil now than ever that's right yeah except that is
this now uh it's imported so the sad part of that is when you start telling people i have this
invention and it works oh if something like that would have worked the important chrysler would
already have it on their cars i have no idea how many times i've heard that line yeah for the best
one and i hate to pick on cowboys but one guy had got bunk bucked off his bronco one too many times
He had a buckle about eight inches wide, and he came up there with his thumbs in his pocket,
and he says, you can run on crude oil and get 90 times the mileage of gasoline?
I said, yeah.
And no pollution?
Yeah.
Man, that is anti-American.
I said, how's that?
Well, we've got to support the government and buy that gas.
I said, aren't you worried about pollution?
He said, no.
I'm going that way, and the pollution is going that way.
sorry folks
thank god we don't all don't share the same books yeah absolutely and thank goodness that
somewhere along the line you know people do hit the wall because oftentimes they don't care about
these choices until the choices that they've made have taken them to the wall and now they
want something that works well years ago before prohibition we had farmers all over the country
that had their own stills they were taking the crop waste putting it in the still and making
alcohol so they could run their farm tractors and their other diesel equipment and the oil
companies didn't like it so they supported the women's suffrage movement to stop alcohol ban
the still we have to get that evil thing out of here oh yeah good old joseph kennedy our first
bootlegger there was a big one uh he was transporting all the booze down for all the
politicians and everybody else who wanted booze with police protection and made him a national
hero. But you don't think the guys in Washington went without booze, do you? Sure, the rest of the
country was supposed to, but they got their booze. And of course, Kennedy's became very famous in
this country and a prestigious family, but for the wrong reason. Yeah, wow. Yeah, that's for sure.
as far as the prohibition
it was all about
shutting down the spills
so farmers couldn't
grow their own crops
to supply fuel
to their equipment
money
it's all about money
follow that money
and you'll follow
the dirty amps
when it comes to
atomic waste
we've been approached
many times
can we get rid of it
yeah we can
we gave a few
demonstrations
of solid atomic waste
disposal
with another inventor
that I know
he came down
and I took care
of the liquid
But after they found out it worked, I received a call saying that if I like living and breathing,
I better not go into that field because there were too many politicians receiving their part of that billion dollars a month
for storing all the atomic waste.
And they did not want competition.
And now those wastes are leeching into water supplies.
Water supplies are leeching out all over the place.
In some cases, big companies don't want to pay.
A good example, one of the girls that worked for me was hired by Kennecott Mining out there in Utah.
And she said they would have an EPA inspector come out,
and they would count how many barrels of contaminants they were burying in their backyard as a mine.
And after they both agreed to it, they'd pay the fine.
It was cheaper than hauling it back to Oak Ridge, Tennessee, and cover it all up.
So how many millions or billions of gallons of toxic waste have we allowed to be buried
because we're too lazy to accept a new technology that works
because we're not paying off the politicians.
And, of course, we've been led to believe
that no such way of mitigating atomic waste exists.
Well, that's what they tell the public.
I've met with many nuclear physicists.
They've all agreed that this is the best, most logical way
of getting rid of atomic wastewater.
We could have gotten rid of a lot of that water from Fukushima,
from Chernobyl and other countries,
even right here in our own backyard but are we invited to work with them no does
our government know that I'm here oh yeah I've been to many meetings outside
of Washington DC over in New Jersey where we had a lot of government
officials there we have the army the Navy every agency EPA they were all there
they saw it running they know it works but they keep coming back saying I'm
sorry we're not allowed to work with you well why finally a few of them came out
and said, well, the government has a fear
that if you ever became as rich as Bill Gates,
you're the kind of person
that would want to change the government,
and that would stop our corporations
from being in control.
We don't want people like you to be rich.
I don't want to be rich either,
and I don't want to be the next Bill Gates.
I want to clean up a planet.
But you can't clean up a planet
when you've got dirty politicians
in the way at every corner.
They don't want all these cars retrofit
to get double and triple their mileage?
They want the road tax.
We need to come up with some new methods
in the sense of new ways of generating revenue or something
so that that becomes a moot point.
Back in the early 80s,
when I first saw these obstacles in front of me,
I sat with many politicians and said,
I would have no objection to opening up a shop
where each person who comes in and puts it on their car
would be certified that they're saving this much money per year,
this many gallons,
and they'd have to pay road tax on the mileage they drove
instead of the gallons they used.
And this, to me, would be fair to everybody.
But the government said it would take too long to pass such laws
and get them through Congress, but it would also hurt too many people.
Because if you have a geet on your car and you don't have any pollution,
you're going to put all these smog shops out of business.
Well, it just basically means that they'll be open to do something else.
I mean, a lot of people look and focus on the loss, and they do not open their mind to, okay, what can we do?
How can we gain?
Because for every loss, there is a gain someplace.
Absolutely.
Look at the cotton gem.
Yes, that replaced a lot of people out there picking.
But let's look at the copy machine.
I saw a video about Xerox years ago where the inventor took it into a law firm that all this firm did with hundreds of secretaries
was sit there and type the same page over and over
so that each congressman and senator could get the exact same page
when they go in the next day.
So these women would work all night long, hundreds of them,
typing with carbon paper.
And if you got the third page, it wasn't quite crispy, clear,
but you could still make out the words.
But they would sit there and make up all these documents night after night
so that they could supply all the documents to Congress.
And the guy who owned the firm said,
I don't see any way that the copy machine is ever going to replace
500 women well sorry to say but uh he was way out in left field as a sure wow uh why we went from
that to the mimeograph machine yeah i remember that in church i was the altar boy and that was
one of my jobs on wednesday was printing up the sunday flyer yes yeah wow uh and that's the thing
about it becoming willing to to try things new uh i mean even you started talking about the
award processing program and we we step by step by step but if you we've gotten to this place of
thinking that's the same type of thinking in the government that that caused them at one point to
want to close down the patent office because they figured everything everything had already been
oh my god can't figure anything else out wow you're listening to talk for food on web at
talkradio.net with adam abraham and we are talking with paul pantone developer of geet
and giving you a preview of a video conversation i don't know that call it a documentary
could be called that but it's to be titled indelible promise and you can find more information
about it as well as additional clips on indeliblepromise.com. It's also where you can
order it. It's produced by moi. And so it goes. But let's talk more or let's hear more from Paul
now. Inventiveness. Inventiveness is what makes our society move forward. But when you've got
companies that have grown rich over prior inventiveness and now they're putting the
brakes on progress i mean to some major here's another good example of we don't want progress
i met with some of the chief engineers that came out from caterpillar waukesha engines uh there
were detroit diesel there were several diesel people there and we showed them a conversion of
waukesha having zero emissions no pollution coming out the tailpipe and they all looked at each other
and said we won't let it fly what do you mean you won't let it fly we'll ban we'll cancel warranties
if anybody puts your technology on our equipment we'll just void the warranty that's against a lot
that's okay sue us the meantime it'll stop all truckers and all other people with heavy equipment
from ever going to you if they know they can't get warranty work done or they won't even be able to
buy parts and i really thought that was a little bit of an idle threat right until i had over 250
000 semis offered after i went up on the internet saying we're ready to start retrofitting semis
and within two weeks i started getting calls saying hey take our name off that list take
our name off that list and why well we were told that if we put a gate on one truck we're not going
going to get any more warranty work done on any of our fleets well those threats were real valid
new york city cab company got a hold of me and said can you put one on a crown vic i said absolutely
he said well we have this model and this model can you get one of each from your local store
we'll pay for them we want them retrofit and we want them driven back here
but we want to fly our drivers out to drive them back so we can validate the mileage right if we
can do that you've got the entire fleet you got 13,000 vehicles to retrofit I drove down to the
nearest dealer that had them I said I'd like to buy that Crown Vic and that one right there
the guy said no problem how do you want to pay for him I said it'll be cash New York City cab
company he went in talked to somebody they talked to the owner a few minutes later the owner comes
out he says are you Mr. Pantone I said yeah he said I've already called the police if you're not
off the property before they get here you will be arrested for trespassing we have the right to
refuse service to anyone and you are anyone we will not sell you or anyone working with your car
you're refusing the sale of two brand new cars you said absolutely i don't want to lose my license
so when the manufacturers tell their dealers we're going to avoid your license and cut you
off as a dealer if you even sell this man apart there's dealerships i can't even go in and buy
an exhaust pipe okay so now here's the possibility of improved gas mileage major reduction in
emissions yeah and the manufacturer would void a warranty if it were put on and now who's pushing
their buttons i mean why do they care i couldn't get straight answers from any of them other than
don't put it on our equipment that was it wow now years ago pretty mean oil company when i made the
news the first day uh they called up and the president of the company personally called up
i had it on tape and he said if you pursue putting gate on cars we'll buy a box of bullets and we'll
find some druggie that'll come out and kill you we don't care if it costs a million dollars
now multiply that times 200 calls in a one day period right but when i called the reporter up
and told him what happened i said ever since i got on your show with the tv show i'm sorry
uh local news i said these death threats came in all day long the story last night about getting
zero pollution is nothing but being threatened by people who are identifying themselves being
with law firms and state agencies and C.A.R.B. or Quality Control, I mean, they're not holding
back. And the reporter said, Mr. Fantone, if you could walk on water, we cannot put
you on the news again. I almost lost my job and my future by putting you on the news last
night. You'll never be on mainstream news again. He hung up. They had gotten to the
point of going through my phone records, which I didn't know anybody could access that easy,
but they did they got a hold of everybody that i knew and told everybody hey if you're working
with paul pantone accidents happen on businesses they called up and said hey there's something
you're doing illegal if not we can make it up if you're dealing with paul pantone after today
your wrecking yard is going to be shut down your car dealership is going to be shut down
we're going to audit you we're going to put you through hell so we've had one reporter after
or another that put us on tv right because they thought it was a novel idea oh this is great
invention it's going to help mankind and i'm supposed to be here to help give the news right
well they didn't realize that the news really isn't the news it's what they're told they can
report so if you catch a new news reporter never done an anchor job before they're going to cover
you they're excited the minute the main guy in their office finds out what you've got then they
they come in blow up and say hey don't ever cover anything like that again our sponsors are oil
companies and politicians we we don't want to upset the people that are our gravy train we don't cover
stories unless they approve it so one after another we got booted off the different stations
fox news now is at guts fox news has covered me in almost every city i've ever gone to
and they come in and say yeah we want to cover it it's news
well it's it's news it's important well it is and it isn't now for years i couldn't get back
on the news and one of the guys working with me came up to me one day and he said how come we
don't have news cameras out here we called them they won't come out he said i'll get them out
here i gotta see this well he went over made a couple telephone calls and he says they'll be
here in about 10 or 15 minutes i said yeah right well i was out there giving a demo for some other
people and all of a sudden these news trucks show up they start raising their booms up the
satellites are being linked up i said you got to be kidding me and they said is this a place where
you're running on fun fuel i said what yeah we were told you run on pickle juice mountain dew we
gotta see the pickle juice uh just a minute give me a minute i ran into the cheriton i ran up to
the kitchen area there and the gal comes up and she's a table for one i said no i just need some
pickle juice to go she said i'm not going to give it to you go to the deli so i went over to the
deli and there was a long line of people it was almost noon they were ready for me outside to go
live at noon with the news right i need a couple glasses real quick pickle juice sweet and sour
sweet and dill and the girl says i'm not going to give it to you unless you promise me you're not
going to drink it in here i promise well they gave me two glasses i ran out and i poured a glass in
each one of them and put the lids on them and i started one engine up first ran it for a little
bit did one interview as soon as i shut that off i started the other one up on pickle juice
with about 10 percent gas in there ran beautiful smooth and clean both of them wow well we made
the news live but it never went any further than colorado springs they uplinked it no other station
in the country wanted to play that footage wow we were supposed to be on the six o'clock news
with better coverage got booted let's talk about how the geet fuel processor actually works and
what it does and what and the principle behind it well it's an acceleration chamber dr william
sue made the comparison uh back in about 1996 97 he worked 20 years of his life on a seven mile
circle underground in beijing and when he came over and looked at ours he held up the rod that's
in the center of it makes it all work and he says uh what you do for 25 cents we do for billions of
dollars he's referring to cost 25 cents in terms of cost of materials versus
billions of dollars to build these particle accelerators the big
difference is yours works you're talking about an acceleration
chamber where accelerator is you found a way of accelerating the molecules and
exciting them and exchanging heat in such a way that you can break it down
it's a total transmutation of elements you're able to produce hydrogen and
helium from crude oil and you release all of these elements in an electrical field that's
self-generated we can't do that if we keep looking over here in a different way and you're looking
at it from a totally different perspective but yours works wow and that means if that nuclear
collider in china is not working the one in switzerland it's just a bigger one and it's not
working either according to him they are lucky if they can come up with a millisecond or two
of actual information from a test this is yours just keeps working and working like energizer
bunny what it allows you to do in real practical terms is to literally run on a fraction of the
fuel the fuel is used what to start the engine is that what the fuel does or is doing something
else we don't get any liquid fuel to our engines or furnaces all it is is a vapor by pulling a
vacuum which has been removed from most books from 1955 on all vacuum technology that would
help mankind was removed actually this is not a plastic bottle it is a combination of gas diesel
and kerosene and if you put this in an electric element underneath it and let it melt the vapors
you're going to get off it are the vapors for gas diesel and kerosene so if you redistill this back
into fuel you have the fuel to run engines power plants whatever you want with no pollution
if you're using a geek so why are we burying all the plastic and garbage bits the government
doesn't want to see this technology is that it replaced they're pumping more oil out they're
buying more oil and they're trucking it and flipping it around so we're talking about i mean
We've got all these issues about plastics and the use of them,
and, of course, the fact that they're not biodegradable.
Okay.
And what you're saying, basically, is they actually are.
A transmutation can occur.
Once you put them through a transmutation process, you now have clean, healthy fuel.
And you have nice, clean, fresh air coming off the tailpipe.
During one of our tests in California, we were running on crude oil from Angola.
And the exhaust vapors that we were getting were cleaner, or the exhaust was cleaner than the air in the room.
We had three to seven parts per million hydrocarbon in the air in the room.
But coming out of the tailpipe, there was zero to one part per million.
We had 21.1 to 23% oxygen coming out the tailpipe and 20% oxygen in the room.
In other words, where we're looking at all of this carbon burning and we're taking down rainforests and stuff,
which are, and trees are the normal producers, processors of carbon dioxide producing oxygen,
we could literally change all of our vehicles into oxygen contributors to the environment.
Well, it was brought to my attention two days ago from a gentleman in California.
He was telling me that the grape growers now are being harassed because of their carbon footprint,
and they're going to be taxed for all the equipment they're using out at the vineyards.
And I said, well, I hope somebody there is smart enough to realize
that it should be offset by an equal or greater amount for all of the production of all these plants.
And if Chevron and Texaco and everybody else can take carbon credits for buying trees in South America,
then why can't the farmers here use their crops to offset what they're producing?
Absolutely. Wow.
Boy, do you see why I jumped at the chance to go back and spend more time with Paul?
The information, the understanding, the knowledge,
this is and should be part of every educational program
from elementary school through college.
college, vacuum technology, plasma dynamics, and plasma physics. These are things that are
available, have been available to us since the beginning of time. The video itself for DVDs
will be available on indeliblepromise.com. We owe it to ourselves as humanity to know this.
so here it is this is what's happening thank you paul his website is geet international.com g-e-e-t
international.com we'll provide a few more pieces of this particular conversation but i got other
stuff too all right there's more stuff to come but that's all for now if you have any questions
or comments or suggestions please email me at adam at talk for food.com in the meantime be aware
okay be open be yourself be courageous and be in love love it all when talk for food returns
here on web at talkradio.net take care now bye-bye
thank you for watching and listening we'll see you next week talk for food is a phylos
MediWorks Production.