Okay, so we are getting to the second part of the test.
I'm going to show you what we have put inside.
We're going to put it inside the back.
We're going to put it inside and we're going to start the tondeur.
I'm going to remove my bouchon.
I'm going to take my bulleur.
Look at the back, I'll show you a little bit of the texture, and here we go.
And here we go.
So, my puller is wide, so I'll show you how it is.
Ok, donc on peut voir qu'il y a toutes sortes de choses qu'on met à l'intérieur.
Donc, ce que je vais faire maintenant, je vais le remettre dedans.
Je refais mon tuyau.
Et voilà.
Donc, je vais resserrer le tout.
Then, I will put the products in it.
I'll take my mattoe noire.
And here.
So, I'm going to put everything in it.
So you can see the texture, and here it is.
So it's done.
I'm going to put my bouchon.
So what I'm going to do, I'm going to start the tondeuse, she's still very hot, so I'm going to add a little bit of water to start the tondeuse.
And here we go.
And that was the test of the Pantone reactor.